Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence - Incoming, Incoming correspondence of 4,326 letters, 235 post cards, and 70 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. There are several circular and mimeographed. 1 Letters signed with initials only and with 1 name only are found at e
  - Cole, Whitefoord (33), Oct. 29, 1946, Oct. 30, 1946, Nov. 3, 1946, Nov. 4, 1947 (post card), June 19, 1948, Sept. 12, 1949, ept. 15, 1949, Dec. 14, 1949, uec. 14, 1949, uec. 17, 1949, Dec. 31, 1949, Dec. 25, 1950, Nov. 17, 1952, Mar. 12, 1954; June 1, 1954, June 5, 1954, June 11, 1954, July 20, 1954 (post card), July 30, 1954 (post card), Feb. 21, 1955, Apr. 3, 1955, Apr. 9, 1955 (post card), Aug. 26, 1955 (to the Editor of the Courier Journal); Aug. 31, 1955, May 2, 1959 (post card), Sept., 1959, Sept. 10, 1959) (post card), Sept. 101 1959, Oct. 28, 1959, Mar. lf, 1960 (to the Nashville Banner); Mar. 14, 1962, Oct. 3, 1962, (n.d.) (post card) (Box 3)
  - Colelllan, Anna (1), Jan. 14, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Collega And Specialist Bureau (1), Dec. 18, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Collins, Charles F. (1), Mar. 10, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Collins, Emma and Family (1), June 30, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Collins, Janet (1), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Conkin, Paul (1), Sept. 25, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Conner, Jane B. (3), eb. 15, 1949, Sept. 26, 1949, (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Conner, Hugh J. (1), Apr. 28, 1941 (Box 3)
  - Coody, A.S. (1), Feb. 29, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Cook, A.B. (1), Dec. 29, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Cook, Emily Hall (3), Apr. 28, 1952, May 18, 1952, May 2, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Cook, John Hutchineen (7), July 8, 1949, Kay 5, 1950, Feb. 28, 1951 (post card), May 3, 1951, July 17, 1951, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Cook, Sterling (2), June 29, 1955, Feb. 9, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Cook, W.W. (2), Oct. 31, 1935, Feb. 4, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Cook, W.W. (2), Nov. 15, 1934 (to Charles S.Shoup), Dec. 5, 1934 (Box 3)
  - Cooney, Bob and Annie Lee (1), Dec. 18, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Anne C. (2), Mar. 29, 1953, Dec. 6 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Bryant S. (14), May 7, 1935, Hay 29, 1944, Sept. 4, 1946, Sept. 17, 1946, Oct. 2, 1946 (post card), Oct. 2, 1946, Nov. 10, 1946 (post card), Dec. 9, 1946, May 16, 1948, Oct. 18, 1949, Dec. 7, 1949, Nov. 7, 1950, Uec. 27, 1950, June 8, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Prentice (3), Jan. 31, 1955, May 31, 1955, Oct. 24, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Wade H. (4), Dec. 13, 1951, Aug. 24, 1954, ept. 4, 1954, Jan. 1, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Cortelyou, John V. (1), Feb. 20, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Costello, H.T. (1), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Cotrell and Leonard, Inc. (1), Kay 26, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Courtney, Wirt (1), Dec. 4, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Cowherd, Nancy H. (4), Sept. 16, 1951, Aug. 23, 1952, Nov. 13, 1952, Jan.D, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Cox, William A. (1), Sept. 6, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Crabb, A.L. (1), Apr. 6, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Crane, Harry W. (2), June 6, 1925, Oct. 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Craver, Mrs. F.N. (3), Mar. 21, 1945, Nov. 28, 1945, Oct. 15, 194? (Box 3)
  - Crawford, R.B. (3), Aug. 4, 1955, Feb. 25, 1959, Mar. 10, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Creed, Howard B. (1), July 15, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Cross, Jeanaette Gillies (1), Aug. 25, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Cross, Jeannette W. (5), July 24, 1952, Aug. 12, 1952, May 15, 1953, Jlly 6, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Crouch, Brockway (1), Aug. 9, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Crow, M.C. (1), Feb. 13, 1946 (Box 3)
  - Crowell, T.I. (1), Feb. 15, 1935 (Box 3)
  - Crowley, Pat (1), May 7, 1942 (Box 3)
  - Crownover, Arthur Jr. (1), Oct. 1, 1935 (Box 3)
  - Crownover, Sias (6), Aug. 6, 1954, Feb. 9, 1955, Mar. 22, 1955, July 1, 1955, July 16, 1955, Apr. 17, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Cruger, Alexander P. (1), June 6, 1936 (Box 3)
  - Cucuel, Bruce L. (1), Oct. 17, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Cummings, G.W. (1), Mar. 22, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Mrs. Briggs S. (1), Jan. 5, 1944 (post card) (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Eileen R. (1), Nov. 25, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Curtiss, Ada H. (4), Jan. 22, 1944, Dec. 5, 1944, Dec. 12, 1944, June 4, 1945 (telegram) (Box 3)
  - Dallenbach, Karl M. (9), Nov. 22, 1949, Dec. 12, 1949 (post card), Feb. 18, 1950, Mar. 25, 1950, June 23, 1951, Apr. 17, 1953, Apr. 30, 1954, Mar. 2, 1956, May 31, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Dalton, Sydney (1), (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Daly, Hosemary (1), Dec. 12, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Danforth, George Edson (2), Jan. 26, 1959, Feb. 3, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Daniel, Harben (1), Jan. 25, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Daniel, Dr. and Mrs. John (1) (Box 4)
  - Darwin, J.D. Jr. (2), July 2, 1951, July 7, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Dashiell, John F. (3), Sept. 28, 1927 (post card), Dec. 13, 1949 (post card), Mar. 5, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Daughety, R. Oswald (1), Nov. 19, 1945 (Box 4)
  - David, Farilla B. (1), June 10, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Davidson, Donald (8), Sept. 20, 1945, Apr. 7, 1946, Feb. 12, 1950, Sept. 22, 1952, May 11, 1956, Nov. 22, 1959, Dec. 13, 1962, Mar. 28, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Davidson, Philip (2), Apr. 1, 1946, Aug. 31, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Davidson, Mr. and Mrs. Philip (1), Nov. 15, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Davis, Clara Jean (37), Mar. 28, 1950, Jan. 26, 1952, Apr. 25, 1952, May 1, 1952, May 5, 1952, May 24, 1952, Aug. 9, 1952, Aug. 13, 1952, Sept. 3, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, (telegram), Nov. 25, 1952, Dec. 6, 1952, Dec. 30, 1952, Feb. 21, 1953; Feb. 25, 1953, Feb. 27, 1953, Feb. 28, 1953, Mar. 6, 1953 (to John Neff), Mar. 16, 1953, Mar. 1?, 1953, Apr. 271953, May 1, 1953, July 16, 1953, Mar. 3, 1954, July 31, 1954, Aug. 16, 1954, Dec. 2, 1954, Dec. 27, 1954; Jan. 27, 1955, May 5, 1955, May 18, 1955, Sept. 21, 1955, Jan. 11, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Davis, J.W. (1), Jan. 10, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Davis, John W. (1), July 29, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Davis, William T. (1), Mar. 2, 1951 (Box 4)
  - DeBord William L. (2), Feb. 13, 1952, (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - de Capriles, Jose R. (1), Nov. 25, 1949 (Box 4)
  - de Courcy, Kenneth (1), n.d.) (Box 4)
  - de la Warr, Frances (1), Mar. 21, 1956 (Box 4)
  - De Laney, Mrs. Lewis (2), June 18, 1945, Sept. 2, 1946 (Box 4)
  - de Vries, E.E. (3), Sept. 29, 1953, Nov. 25, 1953, Feb. 4, 1954 (Box 4)
  - DeWitt, John H. Jr. (2), Dec. 16, 1949, Apr. 3, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Dean, Iris (1), July 21, 1950 (poet card) (Box 4)
  - Dehoney, W.W. (1), Oct. 9, 1944 (post card) (Box 4)
  - Demiashkevich, M. (2), June 11, 1935, June 26, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Dendy, Wm. L. (1), Feb. 10, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Dennett, Elisabeth R. (5), Jan. 31, 1945, July 3, 1952, Sept. 20, 1952, Feb. 3, 1953, Oct. 28, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Densmore, Catherine (1), June 3, 1942 (Box 4)
  - Denny, Collins Jr. (1), Sept. 14, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Dick, Alfred M. (2), ept. 7, 1951, (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Dill, Herbert H. (1), Feb. 28, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Dill, Marshall (1), Jan. 26, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Dillard, Eugene (1), (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Dilling, Elizabeth (1), Jan. 19, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Dingler, Hugo (9), ec. 22, 1949, Mar. 15, 1950, ¥ 223, 1950, Feb. 14, 1952, Mar. 4, 1952, June 10, 1952, Jan. 5, 1953, Feb. 21, 1953, June 2, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Dingler, Martha (13), Mar. 15, 1955, May 12, 1955, Aug. 19, 1955, Oct. 22, 1955, Nov. 11, 1955, Feb. 22, 1956, Mar. 26, 1956, Apr. 16, 1957, Aug. 16,1958, Dec. 20, 1958, June 17, 1959, June 27, 1959, Dec. 2, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Dinkins, H.H.Jr. (1), (n.d.) (post card) (Box 4)
  - Director of Athletics (1), (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Dismukes, Julaan Macon (3), Oct. 24, 1947, Dec. 9, 1947, Aug. 28, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Dodd, Helen (2), Dec. 25, 1949 (post card), Dec. 13, 1951 (post card) (Box 4)
  - Dodge, David C. (1), Apr. 6, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Dog World (1), (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Doherty, Nora DuFrayne (1), Jan. 10, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Donitz (1), Aug. 21, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Donnelly, Francis P. (1), Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 4)
  - Doody, Elizabeth M. (5), Feb. 10, 1944, Nov. 3, 1946, Sept. 21, 1950 (post card), Jan. 1, 1953, Mar. 27, 1953 (Box 4)
  - Dorcus, Roy M. (5), Mar. 9, 1927, Mar. 19, 1935, Sept. 14, 1949, Sept. 26, 1949, Oct. 14, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Dore, Kaye (7), Mar. 28, 1950 (telegram), May 6, 1950 (post card), Apr. 18, 1959, Nov. 19, 1959, June 27, July 4, Nov. 17 (Box 4)
  - Dowward, Woodrow W. (9), July 21, 1944, Dec. 14, 1944, Jan. 29, 1945, Feb. 15, 1945, July 14, 1945, Sept. 19, 1945, Oct. 5, 1949, Nov. 7, 1949, Oct. 17, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Dowell, Spright (1), Apr. 23, 1935 (Box 4)
  - Drake, J.N. (1), Sept 15, 1930 (Box 4)
  - Drissel, Harvey (1), Dec. 18, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Droege, Lee John (1), Nov. 18, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Drown, Lois (4), July 3, 1951, Aug. 4, 1951, Dec. 5, 1955, Nov. 2 (Box 4)
  - Drumm, Alma (1), June 17, 1948 (telegram) (Box 4)
  - Drumm, Ed. W. (2), Nov. 6, 1946, June 17, 1948 (telegram) (Box 4)
  - Drumm, Ed and Alma (2), Nov. 1, 1946, Jan. 4, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Drummond, A.c. (1), Nov. 21, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Du Bose, L.V. (3), June 5, 1952, June 7,1952 (post card), Oct. 20, 19. 54 (Box 4)
  - Du Bose, Martha B. (1), July 30, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Du Buis, Edna M. (6), Nov. 9, 1945, Oct. 17, 1946, Sept. 29, 1949, Oct. 29, 1954, Nov. 16, 1954, Nov. 24, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Dube, Otto (1), Sept. 23, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Duda, Theodore (2), Aug. 6, 1935, Oct. 5, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Deuvu, Mrs. (1), Feb. 7, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Duffy, Elizabeth (11), Feb. 26, 1945, Mar. 4, 1945, Nov. 14, 1945, Jan. 5, 1946, Feb. 13, 1946, Apr. 4, 1946, Feb. 23, 1947, Feb. 28, 1950, Feb. 28, 1950, Mar. 17, 1950, Mar. 24, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Duggan, Jack Dies (1), June 25, 1935 (to H.D. Sims) (Box 4)
  - Duggan, Laurence (1), Jan. 31, 1948 (Box 4)
  - Dumont, W.E. (5), Sept. 28, 1944 (post card), Oct. 11, 1944, Nov. 9, 1944, Mar. 8, 1945, Sept. 7, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Duncan, Edgar H. (1), Nov. 6, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Duncan, R.J. (2), Oct. 10, 1946, (n.d.) (outgoing letter from anborn is on one side of this incoming letter) (Box 4)
  - Dunford, Ralph E. (3), Dec. 20, 1948 (to R.R. Neyland), Dec. 20, 1948, Mar. 29, 1950 (Box 4)
  - Dunlap, Knight (12), Apr. 27, 1924, May 22, 1924, Dec. 19, 1925, Apr. 30, 1926, ept. 21, 1927, pr. 6, 1935, Oct. 9, 1935, Mar. 26, 1939, Feb. 16, 1944, Sept. 10, 1944, Sept. 24, 1944, May 6, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Durant, A.J. (1), Oct. 10, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Durant, Conrad C. (1), Mar. 19, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Datch, Bert (2), Jan. 13, 1955, June 6, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Dwight, Charles A.S. (1), Jan. 14, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Dye, Samuel B. (2), Sept. 13, 1943, Aug. 13, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Eastland, James O. (2), July 22, 1955, Sept. 14, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Eckstein, Gustav (1), May 9, 1933 (Box 4)
  - Edds, D.P. (1), Feb. 28, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Edel, Abraham (1), Mar. 9, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Edwards, Austin S. (6), Jan. 17, 1927, Feb. 15, 1927, Aug. 7, 1930, Sept. 20, 1951, Sept. 29, 1954, Mar. 21, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Edwards, Bill (1), Dec. 18, 1954 (Box 4)
  - Edwards, Mary S. (1), NoT. 5, 1943 (Box 4)
  - Edwards, William M. (1), Feb. 14, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Egmont, Westy (1), Oct. 2, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Eiermann, Geo. E. (8), Mar. 21, 1938, Sept. 8, 1943, Nov. 10, 1943, Dec. 7, 1943, May 8, 1944, Aug. 18, 1944, Dec. 6, 1944, Dec. 28, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Eisenstadt, Evelyn (1), June 21, 1950 (to R.T.Flewelling) (Box 4)
  - Ellison, Margaret (1), Jan. 1, 1952 (Box 4)
  - The Emeriti Census (2), Jan. 31, 1956; Apr. 20, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Engle, Mrs. E. (1), June 18, 1951 (post card) (Box 4)
  - Epsilon Reunion Committee (1), Mar. 1, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Erhardt, Fannie D. (1), Oct. 12, 1933 (Box 4)
  - Erie, Marguerite (4), Jan. 15, 1943, July 7, 1943, Dec. 4, 1943, Feb. 22, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Erickson, John E. (1), July 8, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Ernst, Warren R. (1), Dec. 31, 1949 (Box 4)
  - Ervin, Virginia (1), Nov. 17, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Esbanks, Mozelle V. (1), Feb. 15, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Estes, W.K. (1), Nov. 16, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Estill, Mrs. Henry (1), Dec. 5, 1934 (Box 4)
  - Ethridge, Eugene B. (1), Mar. 1, 1955 (to Bluford Balter) (Box 4)
  - Ettien, Mrs. I.E. (1), Feb. 11, 1947 (Box 4)
  - Eustis, Sudies. (3), Nov. 3, 1945, Nov. 18, 1945 (telegram), July 31, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Evans, David S. (2), Feb. 13, 1952, Dec. 1, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Evans, M.B. (3), June 23, 1944, Dec. 6, 1946, Sept. 9, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Evans, Mary Ann (2), Apr. 16, 1946, June 26, 1946 (Box 4)
  - Evans, Robert C. (1), Jan. 15, 1951 (Box 4)
  - Evans, Thomas M. (2), Sept. 23, 1955, Nov. 17,1955 (Box 4)
  - Everett, P.B. (5), Feb. 28, 1944, July 18, 1946, Mar. 20, 1951, Feb. 13, 1953, May 6, 1953 (to Dorothy Sanborn Sullivan) (Box 4)
  - Everingham, Harry T. (4), Aug. 1955, Sept. 1955, July-Aug., 1956, (n.d.) (Box 4)
  - Erersole, J.B. (1), Nov. 26, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Eward, Gus (2), May 4, 1942, Sept. 29, 1943 (Box 4)
  - Fagan, Myron C. (2), Oct. 24, 1955, (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Fahey, Lawrence P. (1), Dec. 12, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Fain, Tyree (2), July 3, 1949, June 25, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Farber, Morris (1), Oct. 18, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Farley, Mary L. (23), May 6, 1936, Oct. 2, 1944, Dec. 5, 1944, Dec. 17, 1944, Jan. 15, 1945, Feb. 18, 1945, Feb. 19, 1945, Mar. 2, 1945, June l, 1945, Dec. 31, 1945, Feb. 22, 1946, May 8, 1946, July 16, 1946, Aug. 6, 1946, Oct. 21, 1946, Nov. 7, 1946; Feb. 26, 1947, Mar. 26, 1947, Apr. 11, 1947, Sept. 30, 1949, Jan. 6, 1950, Feb. 7, 1950, Oct. 24, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Farlow, Mrs. Merton A. (1), Apr. 14, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Farrell, F.D. (1), Feb. 12, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Feild, G.S. (2), Aug. 27, 1952, May 27, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Fellows, Elizabeth A. (2), Jan. 20, 1946, Jan. 28, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Feltrinelli, Giangiacomo (2), Mar. 31, 1958, Sept. 9, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Fetter, J.F. (2), Mar. 31, 1947, Apr. 29, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Fields, Edward (1), Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Finkelstein, Louis (1), Apr. l, 1946 (Box 5)
  - First American National Bank (3), July 22, 1959, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Fischer, Wilhelm L. (1), May l, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Doug (1), Sept. 2, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Douglas H. (1), July 8, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Fisk University (1), Apr. 13, 1935 (post card) (Box 5)
  - Fisaell, Beatrice (1), Nov. 17, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Fite, Alexander G. (4), Oct. 18, 1949, July 29, 1954, Oct. 15, 1955, June 30, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Fite, John W. (1), Mar. 6, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Fix, Kermit (1), Apr:12, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Fleuriel, Cynthia W. (1), Jan. 17, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Flewelling, Ralph Tyler (6), Nov. 9, 1949, June 20, 1950, June 26, 1950, July 18, 1950, Jan. 8, 1951, Apr. 15, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Flippen, H.E. (1), Feb. 23, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Floericke, Kurt (1), June 24, 1930 (poet card) (Box 5)
  - Floore, Ernest L. (4), Nov. 14, 1945, Oct. 20, 1948, Feb. 23, 1951, June 6, 1950 (post card) (Box 5)
  - Floore, Ernie and Ruth (1) (Box 5)
  - Flygt, Sten G. (3), Jan. 3, 1958, Mar. 11, 1959, Aug. 15, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Flygt, Sten and Lavinia (1) (Box 5)
  - Focht, Carl (4), July 26, 1947, Feb. 12, 1950, Mar. 13, 1950, July 18, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Fodegce, Frida (1), May 27, 1934 (Box 5)
  - Foley Dog Show Organization, Inc. (1), Oct. 27, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Forbes, Cornelia (1), July 30, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Forbes, Esther (2), Apr. 4, 1944, Oct. 13, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Fordyce, Donald N. (1), Oct. 23, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Foresee, Nell (1), Oct. 1, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Forst, John A. (1), Oct. 26, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Forsyth, Gordon (2), Feb. 28, 1935, (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (1), May 21, 1954 (to Mr. Williams) (Box 5)
  - Foster, J.P. (3), May 28, 1942, Dec. 14, 1942, Feb. 14, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Fowler, Mrs. R. (1), Mar. 3, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Fowler, W.E. (1), Sept. 12, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Fox, Charles J. (1), Feb. 24, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Foyle, Christina (1), Nov. 1949 (Box 5)
  - Frampton, A.C. (1), Feb. 14, 1944 (Box 5)
  - France, Louisa F. (1), Feb. 28, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Francis, Anne (2), Mar. 25, 1953, May 16, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Francke, Knno (2), Sept. 12, 1924, Apr. 13, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Frank, Irene Adams (1), Oct. 29, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Frank, John G. (3), Jan. 6, 1949, Oct. 15, 1952 (telegram), Oct. 22, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Frank, Mrs.Richard (4), Apr. 12, 1944, June 5, 1944, Aug. 2, 1944, Mar. 28, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Franklin, James A., Jr. (2), Aug. 8, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Fraser, Cyril V.Jr. (2), May 31, 1954, Oct. 29, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Fraser, G.Jr. (2), Sept. 12, 1957, Oct. 9, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Frazer, Mrs.James s. (1), July 31 (post card) (Box 5)
  - Freeman, R.M. (1), Feb. 26, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Freeman, Warrens. (1), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - French, R.H. (1), Feb. 15, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Frey, Martin J. (5), Mar. 9, 1950, June 13, 1951, July 16, 1951, July 28, 1952, Dec. 4, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Friar, G. Edward (1), Aug. 27, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Friar, Mary B. (2), Jan. 5, 1955, June 26, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Fricke, George R. (1), May 28, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Frizzell, Mary (1), Mar. 22, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Froelich, Mrs. R. (11), Jan. 12, 1944, Jan. 24, 1944, Feb. 24, 1944, Mar. 13, 1944, Apr. 6, 1944, Apr. 15, 1944, Apr. 25, 1944, Aug. 23, 1944, Nov. 8, 1944, Apr. 19, 1946, Sept. 3, 1952 (outgoing letter from Sanborn on other side of this incoming letter) (Box 5)
  - Fulton, James Street (3), Feb. 20, 1928, Feb. 5, 1953, Feb. 5, 1953 (to Harvey Branscomb) (Box 5)
  - Fuqua, V.L. (2), June 20, 1946, June 28, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Furman, Richard B. (1), May 30, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Gailor, Thos. F. (1), Dec. 29, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Galloway, Margarete (40), Sept. 4, 1943, Sept. 14, 1943, Oct. 13, 1943, Dec. 10, 1943, Jan. 20, 1944, Feb. 19, 1944, Mar. 1, 1944, Mar. 17, 1944, Apr. 7, 1944, Apr. 12, 1944, Apr. 25, 1944, May 4, 1944, Mar. 10, 1944, May 13, 1944, May 27, 1944, May 31, 1944; June 13, 1944, June 22, 1944, June 28, 1944, June 29, 1944, Aug. 3, 1944, Sept. 11, 1944,Sept. 25, 1944, Oct. 9, 1944, Oct. 11, 1944, Dec. 7, 1944, Jan. 3, 1945, Jan. 24, 1945, Feb. 13, 1945, Apr. 23, 1945; July 20, 1945, Apr. 16, Aug. 19, Sep. 20, Sept. 22, Nov. 27, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Gamertsfelder, W.S. (1), (n.d.) (to John H. Melzer) (Box 5)
  - Gard, Fred (1), Jan. 18, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Gardner, Edvin. (2), Apr. 29, 1944, Nov. 28, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Gardner, Geo. R. (1), Feb. 10, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Garis, Ron. L. (1), Sept. 3, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Garnett, Charles L (4), June 24, 1954, June 26, 1954, Aug. 4, 1954, Sept. 12, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Garret; M.R. (2), Dec. 4, 1953, Nov. 4, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Garrett, Henry E. (2), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Garshviler, c.o. (1), Xug. 1, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Garth, A.L. (1), Feb. 12, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Garth, Evelyn s. (1), Aug. 15, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Gauthier, Charles J. (1), Mar. 20, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Gebhardt, G.H. (1), Mar. 19, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Geddes, James (1), Apr. 8, 1936 (Box 5)
  - Geldard, .rrank A. (1), Mar. 30, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Gibbs, A.N. (1), Feb. 15, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Gibson, Lida Mae (15), Jan. 2, 1954, Apr. 14, 1954, June 11, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 22, 1954, Sept. 21, 1954, Oct. 6, 1954, Nov. 22, 1954, May 9, 1955, May 20, 1955, May 27, 1955, June 9, 1955, Apr. 26, 1957 (post card), June 5, 1957 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Gilbert, Hortense (1), Sept. 9, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Gilbreath, Mr.and Mrs. Robert F. (1), Oct. 30, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Gilcrist, James (1), Oct. 9, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Giles, W.W. (4), June 3, 1950 (post card), Aug. 16, 1950 (post card), Oct. 4, 1950, (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Gill, Robert s. (1), Oct. 8, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Gill, Wed (1), Feb. 10, 1946 (post card) (Box 5)
  - Gillies, Jeannette W. (1), Oct. 11, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Gilmore, R.C. (2), Feb. 11, 1945, Feb. 19, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Ginn and Company (2), June 19, 19o8, Sept. 5, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Gipson, J.H. (3), Feb. 7, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955, Aug. 1, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Gist, E.B. (1), Oct. 4, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Glen, Saint Mary Nurseries Co. (1), Dec. 18, 1944 (post card) (Box 5)
  - Glover, Frank H. (1), Mar. 16, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Godfrey, Thomas B. (5), Jan. 10, 1949, Apr. 27, 1949, ec. 7, 1949, Dec. 31, 1949, Mar. 28, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Goldgar, Harry (2), Apr. 22, 1944, Mar. 28, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Goldman, Marcus I. (1), Sept. 9, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Gonzales, May Guilbeau (1), Mar. 17, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Gonzalez, Horatio (1), Jan. 6, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Goodale, Hubert D. (1), Sept. 8, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Goodgion, Dorothy S. (1), Nov. 22, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Goodwin, Frank (2), Oct 11, 1943, Jan. 10, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Gotesky, Rubin (1), Feb. 27, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Graeser, Edna (1), Sept. 20, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Grasson, Robert (2), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Gray, Forrest (1), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Gray, Philip (3), Sept. 23, 1957, Mar. 6, 1958, May 21, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Gray, R.V. (1), Dec. 27, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Green, John H. (1), Feb. 15, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Greenaway, Virgil H. (1), July 2, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Greenburg, Grayce (38), Nov. 2, 1949, Nov. 13, 1949, Dec. 16, 1949, Dec. 22, 1949, Jan. 7, 1950, Jan. 25, 1950, Feb. 6, 1950, Feb. 13, 1950, t'eb. 25, 1950 (post card), Apr. 6, 1950, May 30, 1950, June 5, 1950, July 1, 1950, Aug. 3, 1950 (post card), Aug. 7, 1950; Sept. 5, 1950 (post card), Sept. 11, 1950 (post card), Sept. 15, 1950, Nov. 20, 1950 (post card), Dec. 2, 1950, Dec. 28, 1950 (post card), Jan. 4, 1951, Jan. 26, 1951, Feb. 2, 1951, Apr. 6, 1951, May 14, 1951, May 31, 1951, July 18, 1951; July 25, 1951, ept. 8, 1951, Oct. 12, 1951, Nov. 14, 1951, Feb. 5, 1952, Mar. 6, 1952, July 16, 1952, Feb. 24, 1953, Apr. 19, 1957, (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Greene, Theodore M. (2), Oct. 7, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Greer, J.J. (1), Nov. 9, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Gregoire, Mrs. P.L. (1), July 14, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Gregory, Ralph (2), Mar. 1, 1944, Jan. 31, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Gresh, Walter A. (2), Jan. 15, 1952, Jan. 19, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Grigsby, Ethel M. (1), July 6, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Grise, F.C. (1), May 17, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Guepe, A.L. (1), (n.d.) (Box 5)
  - Guin, Margaret (1), Jan. 17, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Gunn, Clarence (1), June 12, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Guntermann, Vivian N. (1), Oct. 31, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Gupton, Wm. (1), Jan. 18, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Hackett, Norman (1), June 15, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Hackett, Ruth (1), Nov. 3, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Hackman, G.W. (3), June 7, 1952, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Hadlich, Hermann (20), Aug. 10, 1903 (post card), June 8, 1927 (post card), Sept. 12, 1945, Oct. 28, 1945, Mar. 21, 1946, Apr. 15, 1946, Hay 31, 1946, June 281946, Aug. 8, 1946, Sept. 25, 1946, Feb. 14, 1947, Feb. 21, 1948, Dec. 14, 1948; Jan. 20, 1949, Dec. 9, 1953, Feb. 25, 1954, June 2, 1954, Feb. 18, 1956, May 4, 1959, Sept. 23, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Hadlock, Mrs.J.H. (1), Jan. 21, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hager, Chester A. (2), Aug. 23, 1949, Sept. 9, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Haggard, Ernest A. (1), Jan. 3, 1950 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Hagood, Lee (1), Sept. 1, 1955 (to Mr.Crovnover) (Box 6)
  - Hahn, Lewis E. (4), July 22, 1958, Oct. 3, 1958 (to Wi1se B. Webb), Nov. 25, 1958, Mar. 30, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Hale, H.C. (1), Oct. 8, 1924 (Box 6)
  - Hall, Douglas (1), June 22, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Hall, Fitzgerald (1), Oct. 19, 1927 (Box 6)
  - Hall, M.M. (1), Feb. 20, 1956 (Box 6)
  - HalleKonrad (3), Dec. 17, 1946, Feb. 7, 1948, May 1, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Hamilton, Shirley (1), Apr. 19, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hammer, Carl (1), Mar. 12, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hammond, Wm. A. (3), May 25, 1927, July 9, 1927, Mar. 11, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Hampton, Charles (1), Aug. 24, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Handy, Dorothy Davies (1) (Box 6)
  - Hannae, Ralston R. (1), Oct. 31, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Hanway, John Howard (1), Jun4, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Hapgood, Elizabeth Reynolds (1), Aug. 11, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hapgood, R.L. (1), Aug. 15, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Haradon, Ralph A. (2), Sept. 10, 1959, Jan. 15, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Hare, Mrs. L.R. (1), Feb. 14, 1955 (to Republican National Comm.) (Box 6)
  - Harper Seed Co. (1), Mar. 5, 1948 (poet card) (Box 6)
  - Harrell, Mrs.James A.Jr. (4), Dec. 7, 1950, Jan. 17, 1951, Jan. 26, 1951, Feb. 20,1951 (telegram) (Box 6)
  - Harrer, G.A. (1), Oct. 18, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Harris, Albert Mason (1), Feb. 8, 1928 (Box 6)
  - Harris, Eugene O.Jr. (1), Nov. 2, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Harris, Marjorie S. (9), Apr. 25, 1925, Apr. 27, 1926, June 28, 1958, May 23, 1959, July 12, 1959, Sept. 7, 1959, Jan. 6, 1960, July 7, 1960, (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Harris, Roy V. (2), June l, 1960, May 26, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Harrison, Mel (1), Apr. 14, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Harrison, Mrs. T.J. (1), Jan. 4, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hart, Alexander, E. (2), Mar. 26, 1955, Mar. 20, 1956 (Box 6)